[
    {
        "Question": "steadily",
        "Answer": "continuously",
        "Options": "constantly"
    },
    {
        "Question": "propagated",
        "Answer": "spread",
        "Options": "multiply"
    },
    {
        "Question": "prohibit",
        "Answer": "prevent",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "resemble",
        "Answer": "look like",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "endorse",
        "Answer": "support",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "susceptible to",
        "Answer": "likely to be affected by",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "hierarchical",
        "Answer": "having several levels of authority",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "demonstrate",
        "Answer": "indicate",
        "Options": "show"
    },
    {
        "Question": "diminished",
        "Answer": "reduced",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "pinpoint",
        "Answer": "identify precisely",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "convey",
        "Answer": "communicate",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "prior to",
        "Answer": "before",
        "Options": "preceding"
    },
    {
        "Question": "a glimpse into",
        "Answer": "a brief view of",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "agitated",
        "Answer": "created movement in",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "terrestrial",
        "Answer": "land",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "disruption",
        "Answer": "disturbance",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "prone",
        "Answer": "likely ",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "little",
        "Answer": "short of",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "profound",
        "Answer": "intense",
        "Options": "far-reaching"
    },
    {
        "Question": "dimension",
        "Answer": "aspect",
        "Options": "size"
    },
    {
        "Question": "contention",
        "Answer": "debate",
        "Options": "claim"
    },
    {
        "Question": "current",
        "Answer": "present",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "roughly",
        "Answer": "approximately",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "justify",
        "Answer": "provide a rational basis for",
        "Options": "support"
    },
    {
        "Question": "affectional tie",
        "Answer": "emotional attachment",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "prime",
        "Answer": "high-quality",
        "Options": "superior"
    },
    {
        "Question": "fastidious",
        "Answer": "demanding",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "boast",
        "Answer": "exaggerate",
        "Options": "puff"
    },
    {
        "Question": "stunning",
        "Answer": "impressive",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "outweighs",
        "Answer": "exceeds",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "attain",
        "Answer": "achieve",
        "Options": "reach"
    },
    {
        "Question": "catastrophic",
        "Answer": "extremely harmful",
        "Options": "disastrous"
    },
    {
        "Question": "norms",
        "Answer": "rules",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "entirely",
        "Answer": "completely",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "exert",
        "Answer": "utilize",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "compilations",
        "Answer": "collections",
        "Options": "put together"
    },
    {
        "Question": "intermittently",
        "Answer": "periodicaly",
        "Options": "regularly"
    },
    {
        "Question": "arise",
        "Answer": "come about ",
        "Options": "emerge"
    },
    {
        "Question": "duplicated",
        "Answer": "copied",
        "Options": "repeated"
    },
    {
        "Question": "desolate",
        "Answer": "deserted",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "optimistic",
        "Answer": "hopeful",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "luminous",
        "Answer": "bright",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "ingenious",
        "Answer": "inventive",
        "Options": "clever"
    },
    {
        "Question": "consistently",
        "Answer": "increasingly",
        "Options": "unvarying"
    },
    {
        "Question": "now and then",
        "Answer": "occasionally",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "interlocked",
        "Answer": "linked",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "accordingly",
        "Answer": "correspondingly",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "barren",
        "Answer": "infertile",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "extended",
        "Answer": "long",
        "Options": "lengthened/ stretch"
    },
    {
        "Question": "repulicate",
        "Answer": "reproduce",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "collaborate",
        "Answer": "work together/ cooperate",
        "Options": "join together"
    },
    {
        "Question": "reluctant",
        "Answer": "unwilling",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "virtue",
        "Answer": "desirable quality",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "discipline",
        "Answer": "punish",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "launched",
        "Answer": "started",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "managed",
        "Answer": "were able",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "corroborate",
        "Answer": "confirm",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "signal",
        "Answer": "communicate",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "placed",
        "Answer": "deposited",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "insisting",
        "Answer": "stating forcefully",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "undoubtedly",
        "Answer": "certainly",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "beckon",
        "Answer": "invite",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "garment",
        "Answer": "article of clothing",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "adjust",
        "Answer": "modify",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "striking",
        "Answer": "noteworthy/ attention getting",
        "Options": "noticeable"
    },
    {
        "Question": "pessimistic",
        "Answer": "negative",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "size up",
        "Answer": "evaluate",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "indefinite period",
        "Answer": "whose end has not been determined",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "dilemma",
        "Answer": "problem",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "in addition to",
        "Answer": "furthermore",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "entitled to",
        "Answer": "give the right to",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "implications",
        "Answer": "consequences",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "brew",
        "Answer": "develop",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "cling to",
        "Answer": "attach",
        "Options": "hold on"
    },
    {
        "Question": "rotates",
        "Answer": "alternates",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "potent",
        "Answer": "powerful",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "incorporated",
        "Answer": "become part of",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "resistance",
        "Answer": "opposition",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "unintentional",
        "Answer": "unplanned",
        "Options": "accidental"
    },
    {
        "Question": "enormous",
        "Answer": "huge",
        "Options": "very large"
    },
    {
        "Question": "transform",
        "Answer": "change",
        "Options": "transition"
    },
    {
        "Question": "rekindled",
        "Answer": "renewed",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "mutual",
        "Answer": "shared",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "obstruction",
        "Answer": "barrier",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "relentless",
        "Answer": "unceasing",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "undergoes",
        "Answer": "experiences",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "aberrant",
        "Answer": "abnormal",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "involved",
        "Answer": "complicated",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "induces",
        "Answer": "brings about/ stimulate",
        "Options": "cause the formation of"
    },
    {
        "Question": "back up",
        "Answer": "support",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "scenario",
        "Answer": "situation",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "on balance",
        "Answer": " overall",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "vastly",
        "Answer": "greatly",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "eliminate",
        "Answer": "get rid of",
        "Options": "remove"
    },
    {
        "Question": "modify",
        "Answer": "change",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "express",
        "Answer": "communicate",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "regrettably",
        "Answer": "unfortunately",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "initiate",
        "Answer": "begin/ start",
        "Options": "first"
    },
    {
        "Question": "cushioned",
        "Answer": "protected",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "preposterous",
        "Answer": "unbelievable",
        "Options": ""
    }
]